[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111030pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 30, "question": "Do you think that they have justification for their anger?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 31, "answer": "Well, I think some are very serious people.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111030pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 40, "question": "And how do you feel about that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 41, "answer": "I sort of think it's cool.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111030pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 67, "question": "In other words, how much is personal responsibility got to come in to play when it comes to finances?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "JJ", "NN", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "IN", "TO", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 68, "answer": "Well, you always say that but they were duped into doing mortgages.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111030pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "NNS", "RB", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 89, "question": "What do you think of that, in particular?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", ",", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 90, "answer": "Well, some of the banks are asking for fees just to keep your money.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111030pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "WP", "POS", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "NNS", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PDT", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "RB", ":", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "VBP", "DT", "JJS", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 97, "question": "What do you agree with?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 98, "answer": "Well, the biggest problem I have with what's happening with the system is the banks, unless you're like somebody like me -- if I want to borrow money, I can borrow all the money I want at the very -- at the rates that are the lowest rates I have ever seen.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111030pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 104, "question": "But they have the money, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 105, "answer": "RUMP: They have the money.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111030pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "NNP", ":", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "POS", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 109, "question": "How do you get through this apparently immovable wall now where the banks have the money but don't want to lend it and the economy is just trapped in hell?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "WRB", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "CC", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 110, "answer": "Part of the problem that the banks have, in all fairness, Piers -- now I'm not a huge fan of the banks because I see what's happening.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111030pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 125, "question": "Is there more that Barack Obama can do as president to unlock this, to move the paralysis?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "RBR", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", ",", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 126, "answer": "You have to let the banks do their thing.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Barack Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111030pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 144, "question": "Did you agree with the bailing out of the banks after Lehman Brothers collapsed?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "VBG", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NNPS", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 145, "answer": "Well, I'll tell you this.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Lehman Brothers"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111030pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 181, "question": "What do you say to that argument?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 182, "answer": "Well -- well, because they didn't really -- I mean, when you think of it, they got very cheap money and they paid it back.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111030pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 186, "question": "Should the government have done that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "DT", "NN", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 187, "answer": "Well, that was the other argument.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111030pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBG", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 220, "question": "Why have you become this talisman for them and what are you making of the Republican race at the moment?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 221, "answer": "Well, I think, first of all, they have some very good people running, and I've become friendly with some of them.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111030pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 234, "question": "But how much of this is done to America just being at the moment oddly inherently weak?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "VBN", "TO", "NNP", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 235, "answer": "We're weak.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111030pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 264, "question": "Why has America stopped doing that kind of thing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "NNP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 265, "answer": "Well, the environmental approvals are impossible.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111030pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 266, "question": "Bureaucracy is crazy here, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "VBZ", "JJ", "RB", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 267, "answer": "The bureaucracy is unbelievable.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111030pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":"], "qSentId": 276, "question": "Why can't the bureaucracy be eliminated?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "RB", "DT", "NN", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 277, "answer": "Well --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111030pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "RBR", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 278, "question": "Why can't somebody get a grip of that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "RB", "VB", "NN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 279, "answer": "It can't be eliminated but it could certainly be made a lot quicker and a lot better and a lot more efficient.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111030pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "RP", "IN", "VBG", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJR", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 290, "question": "So which of all these Republican candidates at the moment do you think has it in him to get America out of this mess?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WDT", "IN", "DT", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 291, "answer": "Well, I have to start off by saying I think any of them would be better than what we have now.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111030pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 310, "question": "How big a problem is this for the Republicans, that the guy that most people think is probably the best option can't get the right kind of traction?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNPS", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJS", "NNS", "VBP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 311, "answer": "Well, look.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111030pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 317, "question": "Why is it, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 318, "answer": "Nobody knows.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111030pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 327, "question": "Is he a bit dull?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 328, "answer": "I don't think so.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111030pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 335, "question": "What do you make of him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 336, "answer": "I think he's a terrific guy.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111030pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 368, "question": "Does Herman -- could Herman Cain do that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "NNP", ":", "MD", "VB", "NNP", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 369, "answer": "I think so.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Herman Cain"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111030pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 399, "question": "It doesn't help anything, does it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 400, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111030pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 412, "question": "What do you think of that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 413, "answer": "You know it's sort of interesting.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111030pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 431, "question": "Do you accept that what he produced is valid?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBZ", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 432, "answer": "No, I don't necessarily.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111030pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":"], "qSentId": 433, "question": "But you believe he probably was born in America?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 434, "answer": "Well --", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111030pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 435, "question": "No?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "aSentId": 436, "answer": "I say he might have been.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111030pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 457, "question": "Is it a sensible thing for him to do?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 458, "answer": "Well, I think it's good for him in the Republican primary.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111030pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", ":"], "qSentId": 465, "question": "Yes, what do you make of him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 466, "answer": "Well, it's --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111030pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "WP", "VBN", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 467, "question": "Because -- I mean in the debates he's pretty shocking, isn't he?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 468, "answer": "I don't know what happened because when you're with him he's great.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111030pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 470, "question": "Is he -- is he articulate?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", ":", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 471, "answer": "He is different.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111030pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "."], "qSentId": 487, "question": "Are you interviewing him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 488, "answer": "I'd love to.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111030pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 490, "question": "Can you put in a good word?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 491, "answer": "Well, I mean, I would.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111030pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 536, "question": "Isn't that exactly the kind of environment you were thinking about and is it possible, given where we are, that you might still run?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "IN", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "JJ", ",", "VBN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 537, "answer": "RUMP: I'm looking.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111030pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 574, "question": "Is that true?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 575, "answer": "Well, I think it's a very bad time to be raising taxes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111030pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 597, "question": "They're not going to get a job and they take that -- them off the unemployment number?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", ":", "PRP", "RP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 598, "answer": "You're a big employer.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111030pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 600, "question": "Do you know?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 601, "answer": "Thousands, tens of thousands of people.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111030pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "CD", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 607, "question": "What is the simple way to stimulate growth and jobs?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "NN", "CC", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 608, "answer": "Well, I have two primary ways.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111030pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 615, "question": "One of the great business men and creator that this country ever produced, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "CC", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "VBN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 616, "answer": "That's true.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111030pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "NN", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 630, "question": "Do you have any stuff, I guess, made for you and your companies in China?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 631, "answer": "I do have stuff made.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["China"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111030pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":"], "qSentId": 635, "question": "A lot?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 636, "answer": "Well, a lot because when you build a building, I mean --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111030pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 644, "question": "What would you say?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 645, "answer": "Well, I'll tell you this.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111030pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "RB", "PRP", ",", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 701, "question": "Something you want to tell me?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 702, "answer": "It was very interesting because it was supposed to be about me, and then I looked at the script, I said, I don't want that about me.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111030pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 714, "question": "Have you sent flowers?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 715, "answer": "No, I haven't, but I hope she does well.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Oprah"]}, "docId": "111030pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 718, "question": "Now what do you think of Oprah?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 719, "answer": "I think Oprah is great.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111030pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "JJ", "VBN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 732, "question": "Is that part of the problem?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 733, "answer": "RUMP: I think we have a country that has tremendous untapped potential.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111030pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "JJ", "JJ", ",", "RB", "JJR", "IN", "IN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 754, "question": "What should the new American dream, the realistic one, be now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", ",", "DT", "JJ", "CD", ",", "VB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 755, "answer": "Well, again, I think the country has unbelievable potential, almost greater than before, if we allow it to happen.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111030pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 773, "question": "And it would seem to me with a population now of, what, seven billion?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "IN", ",", "WP", ",", "CD", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 774, "answer": "Right.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111030pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "``", "NN", ",", "''", "CC", "IN", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 813, "question": "How are you enjoying this new -- this new outburst of young Trumps?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", ":", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 814, "answer": "Well, I've never been a big fan of the name \"grandfather,\" but that's what I am.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111030pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 826, "question": "Are they all fresh faced, excited?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "VBN", ",", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 827, "answer": "They're really good.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111030pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 840, "question": "What does family mean to you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "NN", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 841, "answer": "Well, I think ultimately it's all about family.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111030pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 849, "question": "Is there a remaining great ambition you have?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "DT", "VBG", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 850, "answer": "I think the thing that drives me is I love what I'm doing.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111030pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "PRP", ",", "DT", "JJ", ",", "CC", "RB", "NN", "IN", "POS", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "CC", "VBN", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 873, "question": "How would you like to be remembered?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 874, "answer": "Well, I think somebody that did a really good job aesthetically, I've gotten tremendous reviews on buildings and courses and clubs and all of the things I build, it's very important to me, the aesthetic, but also somebody that's put lots of people to work and created lots of happy families.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]